const quizDataFromFile = [
  {
    "question": "bald",
    "correct": "soon",
    "choices": [
      "soon",
      "never",
      "always",
      "already"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "besser",
    "correct": "better",
    "choices": [
      "always",
      "better",
      "now",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dann",
    "correct": "then (afterwards)",
    "choices": [
      "soon",
      "then (afterwards)",
      "…",
      "not"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gern(e)",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "not",
      "perhaps / may(be)",
      "often",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gestern",
    "correct": "yesterday",
    "choices": [
      "now",
      "yesterday",
      "perhaps / may(be)",
      "no"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "heute",
    "correct": "today",
    "choices": [
      "soon",
      "perhaps / may(be)",
      "today",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "immer",
    "correct": "always",
    "choices": [
      "always",
      "perhaps / may(be)",
      "often",
      "immediately"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jetzt",
    "correct": "now",
    "choices": [
      "now",
      "already",
      "perhaps / may(be)",
      "never"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nicht",
    "correct": "not",
    "choices": [
      "not",
      "today",
      "often",
      "immediately"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nicht",
    "correct": "no",
    "choices": [
      "not",
      "no",
      "often",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nie",
    "correct": "never",
    "choices": [
      "always",
      "never",
      "yesterday",
      "no"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "oft",
    "correct": "often",
    "choices": [
      "soon",
      "better",
      "today",
      "often"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schon",
    "correct": "already",
    "choices": [
      "soon",
      "now",
      "no",
      "already"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sofort",
    "correct": "immediately",
    "choices": [
      "now",
      "no",
      "then (afterwards)",
      "immediately"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vielleicht",
    "correct": "perhaps / may(be)",
    "choices": [
      "perhaps / may(be)",
      "no",
      "now",
      "never"
    ]
  }
];